

Niraj Pahari Software Engineer

How to reach me:

Cell:

+977 984 005 3346

Email:

theniraj23@gmail.com

Github/Gitlab:

nirajpahari

Linkedin:

@nirajpahari

Adress:

St. No. 1, Lakeside, Pokhara, Kaski, Nepal

Education

Kyushu Institute of Technology

Doctor of Philosophy in Advanced Informatics

- Attended from Oct. 2022 to Present
- Research in the field of NLP.

Education History

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang

Master of Engineering in Robotics and Computational Intelligence Systems

- Attended from Aug. 2019 to July 2021
- Research in the field of NLP.

Projects Involved

- Industrial Arm Module for KRAI Platform for ABB IRB 1200
- Document similarity checker application
- Ongoing web application development for industry

Academic Involvement

- Instructor for undergraduate students for Mobile Robots based on ROS, Industrial Robots with Robot Studio and Basics of data science with python libraries.
- Lab Instructor for Computer Programming and Microprocessor.
- Mentor for Internships for exchange students.

Kantipur Engineering College

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering

- Attended from Dec. 2010 to Sept. 2014
- Electives in Bigdata and Al
- Capstone Project: Android based Restaurant solution

Career Summary

Software Developer

Genese Solution Pvt. Ltd. January 2015 - July 2019

- Worked as Backend Developer using Django REST Framework
- Held the responsibility of working with various teams remotely and understanding the requirements of the client and act accordingly.

Part-time lecturer

Soch College of IT July 2016 - July 2019

 Lecturer for Database Management System and Data Warehouse.

Certifications

AWS Certified Developer - Associate

JXZ5MSMC2E1EQBC0

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

Python, C, C++, JS

Frameworks/Systems:

ROS, Django, React, Selenium

References

Dean of School of Engineering, KMITL Email: somyot.ka@kmitl.ac.th

Bikram Adhikari

Chief Technical Officer (CTO), Genese Solution Pvt Ltd.

Email: bikram@genesesolution.com